Contact

7708539538 (Home) pamelamlyon@outlook.com

www.linkedin.com/in/pamela-lyon-ab3023a5 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Nursing

Healthcare

Mental Health

Certifications

Advanced Cardiovascular Life Support (ACLS)

Pediatric Advanced Life Support (PALS)

Basic Life Support (BLS)

Pamela Lyon

RN ED Travel Nurse at AB Staffing Solutions

Calhoun, Georgia

Summary

I am committed to providing complete holistic healthcare to all, especially those residing in under served communities, and have a strong interest in the unique and challenging psychological, cultural, and socioeconomic circumstances of these medically underserved populations.

Experience

AB Staffing Solutions RN ED Travel Nurse March 2020 - Present (4 months) Calhoun, Georgia, United States

Amedisys
Case Management Nurse
January 2020 - March 2020 (3 months)
Canton, Georgia, United States

Calhoun Health Care 8 months

Director Of Nursing August 2019 - January 2020 (6 months) Calhoun, Georgia

Assistant Director Of Nursing June 2019 - August 2019 (3 months) Calhoun, Georgia

GLOBAL DIAGNOSTIC SERVICES, INC. Registered Nurse November 2018 - January 2020 (1 year 3 months) Rome, Georgia

Dalton State College

Nurse Lecturer August 2018 - June 2019 (11 months) Dalton, Georgia

LPN program

AB Staffing Solutions
Travel RN
August 2017 - June 2018 (11 months)

Northside Hospital Emergency Department Registered Nurse February 2016 - August 2017 (1 year 7 months) Canton Georgia

Dalton State College Clinical Instructor September 2016 - June 2017 (10 months) Dalton Georgia

North Georgia Medical Center Emergency Department Registered Nurse July 2015 - March 2016 (9 months) Ellijay Georgia

Georgia Mountains Health LPN March 2012 - August 2012 (6 months) Ellijay Georgia

Canton Nursing Center LPN December 2011 - May 2012 (6 months)

Center For Asthma and Allergy LPN December 2011 - March 2012 (4 months) Symrna, GA

Maxim Healthcare Services LPN January 2009 - December 2011 (3 years)

Correctional Medical Service

LPN

March 2009 - October 2010 (1 year 8 months)

Boonville, Mo

Emory Healthcare

LPN

April 2007 - March 2008 (1 year)

Education

Kennesaw State University

Master of Science - MS, Family Practice Nurse/Nursing · (2020 - 2021)

Dalton State College

Bachelor of Science (B.S.), Registered Nursing/Registered

Nurse · (2014 - 2015)

Dalton State College

Registered Nurse-ASN, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2012 - 2015)

Chattahoochee Technical College

Licensed Practical Nurse, Licensed Practical/Vocational Nurse

Training · (2005 - 2006)